MARK JOENEIL SALAS

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING ASSOCIATE

CONTACT

09053931024

markjoeneil.salas@gmail.com

Tacloban City

RELEVANT LINKS

PORTFOLIO: markjoeneilsalas

LINKEDIN: <u>markjoeneilsalas</u>

GITHUB: markjoeneilsalas

KEY SKILLS

Web Design Responsive Design

Graphic Design Testing and Debugging
Communication skills. Time management.
Interpersonal skills. Graphic Design

Front End: HTML, CSS and Javascript

Back End: PHP

Database: MYSOL

Framework: REACTJS, REACT NATIVE,

LARAVEL and BOOSTRAP

Collaboration Tools:

Microsoft Office, Zoom, Messenger

and Skype.

EDUCATION

Kodego Bootcamp

Full-Stack Web Development

2023 - 2023

JE Mondejar Computer College

BS - Business Administration Major in Marketing Management2019 - 2023

ACLC College

BS - Information Technology Major in Programming 2018 - 2019

CERTIFICATES

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER (Kodego) RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN (Sololearn) PYTHON FOR BEGINNERS (Sololearn) BASIC HTML (Sololearn)

PROFILE

As a talented and committed web developer with knowledge of HTML, CSS, javascript, javascript framework Reactjs, React Native, laravel and Css Framework in Bootrap and minimal in Tailwind, I have experience building responsive websites that are aesthetically pleasing and user-friendly, and I'm passionate about applying my technical abilities to create creative and effective solutions. with a dedication to remaining current with the newest web development techniques and a great attention to detail.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Manager

GaL Travel Services

2023-2023

- · Design strategy and set goals for growth.
- As part of my marketing strategy, I propose to the owner that she create a responsive website to increase sales and reach.
- Currently working on their Management system using Laravel

Freelance Web Developer

ALG CTPL Insurance

2022-2022

 Created their website using template and added several front end design using html, css and javascript.

Freelance Graphic Designer and Computer Technician 2016-Present

- Working on both print and digital projects based on the client's requirements.
 understanding and comprehending client instructions, completing design work on schedule and within a set budget.
- Servicing, maintaining, troubleshooting, and customer repair for computer systems of the clients.
- Experience in Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma and Canva

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Kodego - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

₋igtas

Feb. 2023-March 2023

- $\bullet \quad \text{Technology Used: Html, Css, Javascript, Boostrap, Github.} \\$
- Created this whole project alone using my front end skills.

Kodego - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

CookReady

April 2023-May 2023

- Technology Used: Html, Css, Javascript, Boostrap, Github, Api, Zoom and Messenger for the collaboration.
- Provide front end code and back end code during development period.
- As a team, we successfully built this eCommerce project from the ground up by leading the team by supporting one another for the front end and back end of the website.

Kodego - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Unitop Management System

May 2023-June 2023

- Technology Used: Blade, Css, Javascript, Boostrap, Laravel, Api and Php.
- I Provided both Front end code and Back end code during the development of the website.
- Because of our effective teamwork and coordination, we were able to construct
 this management system and, in order to address the client's issue, this project
 from scratch.